# Joey Giesbrecht

403-894-9823

joey.giesbrecht6@gmail.com

Barnwell, AB, T0K 0B0

#### **Profile**

Over 4 years of experience in the work force. I would best describe myself as a very hard worker/fast learner and someone who you can trust when things need to get done. On my spare time I play basketball and coach basketball for a high school team in the winter.

#### **Experience**

**Skid-steer / Piler operator** <u>Lamb Weston</u> October 2020 - Present

- Operated a skid-steer to haul potatoes from the plant into a tub which would later fill semi-trucks.
  Got so efficient that I was often called upon to supervise operations
- Often did maintenance on machinery
- · During harvest was trusted to operate a piler to get potatoes from the semis back into the plant

**Shop Labourer** Chinook Carriers, Taber November 2019 - October 2020

- Did basically whatever was needed to be done at the shop which ranged from cleaning trailers to patching semi-tires to repairing brakes and everything in-between
- · During harvest worked as a tipper which involved a lot of difficult physical labor and long days
- Obtained a loader license

## **Fulfillment and Cashier**

Walmart, Taber

April 2018 - October 2019

- Dealt with customers on a daily basis which improved my people skills and also learned how to deal with customers that were not so polite
- Got up to 1400 scans per hour as a cashier
- Was promoted to a fulfillment position where I increased productivity through unloading trucks and stocking shelves

### **Education**

- High School diploma from St.Marys Taber
- CIT degree Lethbridge College

**Skills** Hard Working Fast Learner Good technical skills Friendly

Positive attitude Work well in teams Organized

# **Technical Skills**

-DBMS -MySQL -C++ -C# -HTML

-Java -JavaScript